[
  {
    "question": "obvious",
    "correctAnswer": "patent"
  },
  {
    "question": "fatherly; fatherlike",
    "correctAnswer": "paternal"
  },
  {
    "question": "the science of diseases",
    "correctAnswer": "pathology"
  },
  {
    "question": "the male head of a family or tribe",
    "correctAnswer": "patriarch"
  },
  {
    "question": "a person of noble birth; an aristocrat",
    "correctAnswer": "patrician"
  },
  {
    "question": "to treat as an inferior; to condescend to",
    "correctAnswer": "patronize"
  },
  {
    "question": "scarcity",
    "correctAnswer": "paucity"
  },
  {
    "question": "a minor offense",
    "correctAnswer": "peccadillo"
  },
  {
    "question": "boringly scholarly or academic",
    "correctAnswer": "pedantic"
  },
  {
    "question": "unimaginative; banal",
    "correctAnswer": "pedestrian"
  },
  {
    "question": "negative; disparaging",
    "correctAnswer": "pejorative"
  },
  {
    "question": "a strong tate or liking for something; a predilection",
    "correctAnswer": "penchant"
  },
  {
    "question": "sorry; repentant; contrite",
    "correctAnswer": "penitent"
  },
  {
    "question": "thoughtful and sad",
    "correctAnswer": "pensive"
  },

  {
    "question": "a bitter conteraccusation, or the act of making a bitter counteraccusation",
    "correctAnswer": "recrimination"
  },
  {
    "question": "fragrant",
    "correctAnswer": "redolent"
  },
  {
    "question": "unnecessarily repetitive; excessive; excessively",
    "correctAnswer": "redundant"
  },
  {
    "question": "to prove to be false; to disprove",
    "correctAnswer": "refute"
  },
  {
    "question": "to say again; to repeat",
    "correctAnswer": "reiterate"
  },
  {
    "question": "to banish; to send away",
    "correctAnswer": "relegate"
  },
  {
    "question": "continuous; unstoppable",
    "correctAnswer": "relentless"
  },
  {
    "question": "to release or let go of; to surrender; to stop doing",
    "correctAnswer": "relinquish"
  },
  {
    "question": "to argue against; to protest; to raise objections",
    "correctAnswer": "remonstrate"
  },
  {
    "question": "a rebirth or revival",
    "correctAnswer": "renaissance"
  },
  {
    "question": "to give up formally or resign; to disowen; to have nothing to do with anymore",
    "correctAnswer": "renounce"
  },

  {
    "question": "a shared principle or belief",
    "correctAnswer": "tenet"
  },
  {
    "question": "experimental; temporary uncertain",
    "correctAnswer": "tentative"
  },
  {
    "question": "filmsy; extremely thin",
    "correctAnswer": "tenuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "using no unnecessary words; succint",
    "correctAnswer": "terse"
  },
  {
    "question": "the study of God or religion",
    "correctAnswer": "theology"
  },
  {
    "question": "a prolonged, bitter speech",
    "correctAnswer": "tirade"
  },
  {
    "question": "sluggishness; inactivity; apathy",
    "correctAnswer": "torpor"
  },
  {
    "question": "a standard; a test of authenticity or quality",
    "correctAnswer": "touchstone"
  },
  {
    "question": "to praise highly; to brag publicly about",
    "correctAnswer": "tout"
  },
  {
    "question": "to go beyond or above; to surpass",
    "correctAnswer": "transcend"
  },
  {
    "question": "to violate (a law); to sin",
    "correctAnswer": "transgress"
  },
  {
    "question": "not staying for a long time; temporay",
    "correctAnswer": "transient"
  },
  {
    "question": "fear; apprehension; nervous trembling",
    "correctAnswer": "trepidation"
  },
  {
    "question": "shameful wickedness; depravity",
    "correctAnswer": "turpitude"
  },

  {
    "question": "sharp; shrewd",
    "correctAnswer": "acute"
  },
  {
    "question": "stubborn; unyielding; competely inflexible",
    "correctAnswer": "adamant"
  },
  {
    "question": "to speak to; to direct one's attention to",
    "correctAnswer": "address"
  },
  {
    "question": "follower; supporter; believer",
    "correctAnswer": "adherent"
  },
  {
    "question": "to scold gently; to warn",
    "correctAnswer": "admonish"
  },
  {
    "question": "skillful; dexterous; clever; shrewd; socially at ease",
    "correctAnswer": "adroit"
  },
  {
    "question": "wild or excessive admiration; flattery",
    "correctAnswer": "adulation"
  },

  {
    "question": "action independently",
    "correctAnswer": "autonomous"
  },
  {
    "question": "greed; excessive love of riches",
    "correctAnswer": "avarice"
  },
  {
    "question": "to claim; to declare boldly; to admit",
    "correctAnswer": "avow"
  },
  {
    "question": "like an uncle, especially a nice uncle",
    "correctAnswer": "avuncular"
  },
  {
    "question": "off course; twisted to one side",
    "correctAnswer": "awry"
  },
  {
    "question": "a self-evident rule or truth; a widely accepted saying",
    "correctAnswer": "axiom"
  }
]